viralsuccessnetwork.com 2017-06-22

# Privacy Policy

This site (the "Site") is owned by Viral Success Network, LLC, a Virginia limited liability company ("us," "we," or "Company"). We created this Privacy Policy ("Privacy Policy") to explain how we use the information we collect on the Site. This Privacy Policy is only applicable to the Site, and not to any other websites that you may be able to access from the Site, each of which may have data collection, storage, and use practices and policies that differ materially from this Privacy Policy.

We automatically track and collect the following categories of information when you visit our Site: 1) IP addresses; 2) domain servers; 3) types of computers accessing the Site; and 4) types of web browsers used to access the Site (collectively "Traffic Data"). Traffic Data is anonymous information that does not personally identify you but is helpful for marketing purposes and for improving your experience on the Site. We also use "cookies" to customize content specific to your interests.

Our Site provides a range of products and services for you to use in connection with marketing campaigns (collectively, the "Marketing Tools"). In order for us to be able to contact you about your use of the Site and Marketing Tools, we require you to provide us with certain information that personally identifies you ("Personal Information"). Personal Information includes the following categories of information: 1) Contact Data (such as your name, company name, contact information, telephone number, email address, and login name); 2) Financial Data (such as the credit/debit account information for the account you want to establish for billing purposes); and 3) Transaction Data (for example, the name of the person who referred you to us, the names and contact information for people you refer to us, data about specific marketing campaigns and results, consumer contact information such as email addresses and phone numbers, and related marketing materials). If you communicate with us by e-mail, post messages to any of our blogs, chat groups, bulletin boards, or forums, or otherwise complete online forms, any information provided in such communication may be collected as Personal Information.

We use Personal Information in the following ways: 1) to enable you to use our Site and Marketing Tools; 2) to contact you about our Site, Marketing Tools, and other related products and services in which we think you may be interested; and 3) to customize and tailor your experience on our Site.

We do not sell, license, transfer, and/or share the billing information we collect from you, other than for billing purposes. We use an unaffiliated, credit card processing company to process your payments. We transfer your payment information—and you authorize us to do so—to this company solely for this purpose. The company does not retain, share, store, or use your personally identifiable information for any other purposes. We use the Transaction Data we collect to enable users to conduct marketing campaigns, test and analyze results, create campaign-related marketing materials, and to calculate commissions. We also collect and analyze non-personally identifiable Transaction Data and the associated IP address to help us improve our Site and Marketing Tools.

Additionally, the registered member that referred you to our Site is able to view your email address. Registered members can also display the name and telephone number for the person who referred them to our Site, as well as the following information about members of their team (i.e. referrals who become registered users of our Site): name, telephone number, login name, and email address.

You may choose not to provide us with any Personal Information. In such an event, you will not be able to access and use our Site, Marketing Tools, or some of the services it provides.

We may also (and you authorize us to) disclose your Personal Information to: a) comply with a court order or other legal process or inquiry; b) protect our rights or property; or c) enforce our Terms and Conditions. Your Personal Information is stored on secure servers that are not accessible by third parties. We provide you with the capability to transmit your Personal Information via secured and encrypted channels if you use a similarly equipped web browser.

To confirm that your Contact Data and Financial Data are correct and up-to-date, you may review and update it by submitting a support ticket.

The Site contains links to other websites. We are not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such websites. We also make blogs, chat rooms, forums, message boards, and news groups available to you. Please understand that any information that is disclosed in these areas becomes public information. We have no control over its use and you should exercise caution when deciding to disclose your Personal Information.

This Site is directed at teenagers and adults and not to children under the age of 13. We do not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children under the age of 13, nor do we knowingly distribute such information. We do not knowingly allow children under the age of 13 to publicly post or otherwise distribute personally identifiable contact information through our website. Similarly, because we do not collect any personally identifiable information from children under the age of 13, we do not condition the participation of a child under 13 in activities on providing personally identifiable information. If we become aware that we have inadvertently received personally identifiable information from someone under the age of 13, we will delete such information from our records. If we change our practices in the future, we will obtain prior, verifiable parental consent before collecting any personally identifiable information from children under the age of 13.

We have implemented a number of security measures to help protect against the loss, misuse, or modification of information we've collected from you. Your Personal Information is transmitted to and stored on servers that we have taken steps to protect from unauthorized access or intrusion. We do not ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to us. You acknowledge and assume this risk.

We reserve the right, at any time and without notice, to add to, change, update, or modify this Privacy Policy, simply by posting such change, update, or modification on the Site and without any other notice to you. Any such change, update, or modification will be effective immediately upon posting on the Site. In the event of substantive changes to this Privacy Policy, the new terms will be posted to the Site, you will be required to affirmatively assent to its terms, and you may also be notified by email. If any modification is unacceptable to you, your only recourse is not to use the Site and Service and to request an immediate termination of your membership. Your express consent or continued use of the Site or our Service following posting of a change notice or new Privacy Policy on the Site will constitute binding acceptance of the changes.

This site is owned and operated by **Viral Success Network, LLC**  
3618 Alderwood Way  
Chester, Virginia 23831
